Finding Aid for the Randall Stewart Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Randall Stewart Papers
1932-1967
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0420
1.26 linear_feet
Randall Stewart Chronology
1896 Born in Fayetteville, Tennessee, July 25
1898 His family moved to Nashville where he grew up and was educated
1917 Was graduated from Vanderbilt University as Founder’s Medalist
1917-1920 Instructor of English at the University of Oklahoma
1918 Served briefly in the armed forces
1920 Married Cleone Odell in Oklahoma City
1921 Awarded master of arts degree by Harvard University
1921-1922 Instructor, U. S. Naval Academy
1922-1925 Assistant Professor, University of Idaho
1927-1931 Instructor, Yale University
1930 Awarded doctor of philosophy degree by Yale
1931-1934 Assistant Professor, Yale
1932-1939 Associate Editor, New England Quarterly
1934-1937 Professor, Vanderbilt
1937-1955 Professor, Brown University
1943 Guggenheim Fellow
1947-1948 Visiting Professor, Yale University
1949-1950 Chairman, Department of English, Brown
1949-1950 Visiting Professor, Connecticut College
1951 Chairman, American Literature Group, Modern Language Association
1955-1963 Professor of English and Chairman, Department of English, Vanderbilt University
1956 Fugitive Reunion
1958 Mrs. Harold S. Vanderbilt Literary Symposium established
1963-1964 Professor, Vanderbilt
1964 Died June 17
- Correspondence - Outgoing, chronologically arranged, Nov. 23, 1955 to Oct. 1, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1-18)
  - to Jesse Wills with enclosures of two letters dated Oct. 25, 1955, Nov. 23, 1955
  - Red (R. P. Warren), Jan. 25, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - John C. Ransom, Jan. 25, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - John L. Stewart, Jan. 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen Tate, Feb. 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Red (R. P. Warren), Feb. 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Andrew Lytle, Feb. 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cleanth Brooks, Feb. 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - John C. Ransom, Feb. 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - John C. Ransom, Feb. 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Isabel Howell, Feb. 26, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allen Tate, March 6, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - form letter to Fugitives and inter-locutor critics, March 6, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Robert E. Spiller, March 7, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - form letter to Ransom, Davidson, Tate, Warren, Moore, Elliott, Brooks, Lytle, March 11, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - John C. Ransom, March 13, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, March 13, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Donald Davidson, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Red (R. P. Warren), March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Merrill Moore, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cleanth Brooks, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Andrew Lytle, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - William Y. Elliott, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Willard Thorp, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Frank Owsley, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Louise Cowan, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Robert D. Jacobs, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - William Y. Elliott, March 22, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Merrill Moore, March 26, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum to Ransom, Davidson, Tate, Warren, Elliott, Wills, Stevenson, Curry, Hirsch, Starr, March 26, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Vincent L. Eaton, March 29, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Rock, April 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alec B. Stevenson, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, April 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum to the Chaneellor, April 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - John C. Ransom, April 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cleanth Brooks, April 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Overton Williams, Bursar, April 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - William Y. Elliott, April 24, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Harold S. Vanderbilt, April 24, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allen Tate, April 26, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alec B. Stevenson, May 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Harvie Branscomb, May 7, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Harold S. Vanderbilt, May 7, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Overton Williams, May 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Louis Rubin. 2 copies, one with Rubin’s answer, May 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Isabel Howell, May 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fannie Cheney, May 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ellen and Jesse Wills, May 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alec B. Stevenson, May 10, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Charles M. Coffin, May 15, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - R. E. Amacher, May 16, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dorothy Bethurum, May 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allen Tate, May 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dr. O. C. Carmichael. Enclosure of 2 copies of letter from Donald Davidson to A. F. Kuhlman dated May 11, 1956, May 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - LeRoy P. Graf, May 22, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ralph Morrissey, May 24, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - John Marshall, June 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - John L. Stewart, June 2, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Louis Rubin, June 2, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Louis Rubin, June 2, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - John Marshall, June 4, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Louis Rubin, June 6, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - John Marshall, July 5, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Louis Rubin, Sept. 18, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Vincent L. Eaton, Oct. 29, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - John L. Stewart, Nov. 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Louis Rubin, Dec. 3, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Louis Rubin, Dec. 11, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Louis Rubin, Dec. 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - John Marshall, Dec. 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Overton Williams, Dec. 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Richmond Beatty, Feb. 15, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Richmond Beatty, Feb. 22, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Joseph. J. Jackson, Feb. 26, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Richmond Beatty, Feb. 26, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - H. Lloyd Stowe, March 22, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Overton Williams, April 4, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - H. Lloyd Stowe, April 4, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - John Ransom, April 5, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Leonard B. Beach, May 22 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Coleman Harwell, Sept. 4, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Harvey Breit, Sept. 5, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Maurice Dolbier, Sept. 5, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Coleman Harwell, Sept. 16, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Louis Rubin, Sept. 20, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - John C. Ransom, Sept. 27, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Raymond Walters, Jr, Oct. 2, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - John Fay, Oct. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Kenneth C. Crabbe, Oct. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - George A. Doss, Jr., Oct. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Mrs. Anna C. Hunter, Oct. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Keith Coulborn, Oct. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Daisy Tucker, Oct. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Truman Stacy, Oct. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Frank Harris, Oct. 4, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - A. J. Skelton, Oct. 4, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Edith Copeland, Oct. 5, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Gerald R. Ashford, Oct. 8, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12.5)
  - Mrs. Marion H. Broaddus, Oct. 8, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Al Lester, Oct. 8, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bob Phillips, Oct. 8, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - R. P. Schlabach, Oct. 8, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Mrs. Charlotte Walker, Oct. 8, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Allen Tate, Oct. 24, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Red." (R. P. Warren), Oct. 24, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Louis Rubin, Nov. 5, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Participants in the Fugitive Conference, Nov. 13, 1957
  - Participants in the Fugitive Conference. F 14. With replies from Fugitives. 2 copies, Nov. 15, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mrs. Frank L. awsley, Sr, Nov. 15, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mrs. Alfred Starr, Nov. 15, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mrs. Merrill Moore, Nov. 15, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - John E. Drewry, Nov. 15, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - NEA Service, Inc, Dec. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - King Features Syndicates, Dec. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - McClure Newspaper Syndicate, Dec. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Mrs. Merrill Moore, Dec. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - William Y. Elliott, Dec. 9, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Louis Rubin. Fr 16. ’, Dec. 16, 1957
  - Harvie Branscomb, Dec. 19, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Allen Tate, Jan. 10, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Red" (R. P. Warren), Jan. 10, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - John C. Ransom, Jan. 10, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Louis Rubin, Jan. 11, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Allen Tate, Jan. 17, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - William C. Cobb, Jan. 17, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Coleman Harwell, Jan. 20, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Louis Rubin, Feb. 1, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Donald Ellegood, April 29, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Louis Rubin, Dec. 3, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Louis Rubin, Dec. 10, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - John C. Ransom, Dec. 30, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Louis Rubin, Jan. 6, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Marguerite Wriston, Jan. 12, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Allen Tate, Aug. 3, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Allen Tate, Sept. 27, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chancellor Branscomb, Oct. 1, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Form letter to newspaper Editors, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Holograph draft of letter to editors, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Correspondence - Incoming, chronologically arranged, March 2, 1932 - Dec. 4, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19-48)
  - Adams, Dick, May 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Amacher, Anne, May 13, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Amacher, Anne, March 17, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Anderson, Charles R, May 4, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Baker, Carlos, May 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Beatty, Richmond C, Feb. 5, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Beatty, Richmond C, Feb. 23, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bethurum, Dorothy, March 12, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bethurum, Dorothy, April 16, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bethurum, Dorothy, May 13, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bethurum, Dorothy, June 3, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bethurum, Dorothy, Nov. 19, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bethurum, Dorothy, May 21, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Blanchard, Harold H., May 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bradley, Sculley, May 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, March 13, 1956 to Henry Luce (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, March 28, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, April 9, 1956 to Ransom (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, May 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, May 22, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, May 28, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, June 12, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, June 13, 1956 to Willard Thorp (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, June 26, 1956 to John Marshall (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, July 10, 1956 to John Marshall (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, April 10, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Branscomb, Harvie, n.d (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Breis, Harvey, April 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Brooks, Cleanth, Nov. 10, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brooks, Cleanth, Feb. 16, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Brooks, Cleanth, April 18, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Brown, Francis, Sept. 13, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Caesar, Kathleen, Feb. 5, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Carmichael, Oliver C, May 31, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Cheney, Fannie, Feb. 21, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cobb, William C, Jan. 5, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Cobb, William C, Jan. 12, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cobb, William C, Jan. 12, 1956 to Robert McGaw (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cobb, William C, Feb. 28, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cobb, William C, March 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cobb, William C, June 13, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cobb, William C, Jan. 15, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cobb, William C, Jan. 15, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Coffin, Charles M, May 7, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Cohen, Barbara, April 8, 1956 to Robert McGaw (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Copeland, Edith, Oct. 9, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Cowan, Louise, Nov. 21, 1957. F 43. n.d (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Cunningham, James V, May 11, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Daley, Elizabeth Gill, May 30, n.d (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Davidson, Donald, May 11, 1956 to Dr. A. F. Kuhlman. 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Davidson, Donald, June 3, 1956 to Geoffrey Moore (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Dickey, Hervey, May 2, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Drewry, John E, Nov. 26, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Eaton, Vincent L, March 23, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Eaton, Vincent L, March 30, 1956 to Overton Williams (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Eaton, Vincent L, Oct. 24, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Ellegood, Donald, March 18, 1958 to Donald Davidson (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Ellegood, Donald, April 25, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Elliott, William Y, Nov. 25, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Elliott, William Y, Feb. 27, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Elliott, William Y, March 27, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Elliott, William Y, March 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Elliott, William Y, April 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Elliott, William Y, Dec. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Emerson, O. B, April 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Faulkner, Claude W, May 4, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Faverty, Fred, May 7, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Foster, Elizabeth, May 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Gerber, John C, Jan. 2, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Graf, LeRoy P, May 3, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Halpert, Violet, May 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Harwell, Coleman, Sept. 9, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Harwell, Coleman, Sept. 18, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Harwell, Coleman, Feb. 20, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Hirsch, Goldie, Oct. 30, 1955 to Merrill Moore (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Howell, Isabel, Feb. 28, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Hunter, Anna C, Oct. 7, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Hunting, Robert, May 2, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Jackson, William A, April 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Jacobs, Robert D, March 25, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Kazin, Alfred, May 9, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Koller, Kathrine, May 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Kuhlman, A. F, April 18, 1956 to Donald Davidson-2 copies (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Luce, Henry R, March 17, 1956 to President Branscomb (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Lynn, Justine, Feb. 3, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Lynn, Justine, May 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Lynn, Justine, May 11, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Lytle, Andrew, Nov. 4, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Lytle, Andrew, Feb. 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Lytle, Andrew (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - MacLean, Kenneth, May 3, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Marshall, John, March 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Marshall, John, April 18, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Marshall, John, May 24, 1956 to Rubin (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Marshall, John, June 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Marshall, John, June 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Marshall, John, July 3, 1956 to Branscomb (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Marshall, John, July 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Marshall, John, July 10, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Marshall, John, Dec. 12, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Marshall, John, April 4, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Marshall, John, April 18, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - McGaw, Robert M, Jan. 10, 1956 to William C. Cobb (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - McGaw, Robert M, March 8, 1956 to Jack DeWitt (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - McGaw, Robert M, March 29, 1956 to Ransom, Tate, and Warren (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - McGaw, Robert M, March 30, 1956 to Caedmon Sales Corp (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - McGaw, Robert M, March 30, 1956 to Barbara Cohen and Marianne (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - McGaw, Robert M, April 11, 1956 to Jack DeWitt (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - McGaw, Robert M, April 25, 1956 to Barbara Cohen (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Moore, Geoffrey, Feb. 20, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Moore, Geoffrey, May 23, 1956 to Donald Davidson (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Moore, Merrill, Oct. 27, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Moore, Merrill, Oct. 29, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Moore, Merrill, Dec. 5, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Moore, Merrill, April 11, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Moore, Merrill, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Moore, Merrill, April 27, 1956. 2 letters (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Moore, Merrill, April 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Moore, Merrill, June 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Moore, Merrill, June 4, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Moore, Merrill, Jan. 21, 1957 to Mary O. Abbott (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Moore, Merrill, Sept. 10, 1957 to Harvie Branscomb (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Moore, Merrill, n.d (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Moore, Mrs. Merrill, Nov. 25, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Moore, Mrs. Merrill, Jan. 22, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Morison, S. E, March 2, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Morrissey, Eleanor F, May 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Nesbitt, George, May 4, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Owsley, Frank L, March 15, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Owsley, Harriet C, Nov. 24, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Pearce, Roy, Aug. 29, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Pearson, Norman H, Jan. 29, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Peck, Genevieve for Merrill Moore, Feb. 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Peck, Genevieve for Merrill Moore, March 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Phillips, Bob, Jan. 28, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Pomfret, Jack, April 26, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Purdy, Rob Roy, June 21, 1957 to Rubin (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Ransom, John C, Oct. 29, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ransom, John C, Feb. 7, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ransom, John C, Feb. 18, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ransom, John C, April 2, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ransom, John C, May 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Ransom, John C, May 26, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Ransom, John C, March 27, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Ransom, John C, Oct. 18, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Ransom, John C, Nov. 19, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Ransom, John C, Feb. 25, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Ransom, John C, March 3, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Ransom, John C, Feb. 1, n.d (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Rhind, Flora M. (of Rockefeller F.), Oct. 18, 1955 to Robert Spiller (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rock, Virginia, April 4, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., March 22, 1955 to Huntingdon Cairns (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., May 27, 1955 to John Marshall (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., July 19, 1955 to John Marshall (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Oct. 10, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Dec. 1, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., March 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., March 22, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., April 16, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., April 24, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., May 29, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., June 5, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Sept. 13, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Sept. 19, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Nov. 29, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Dec. 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Dec. 14, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Jan. 10, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., June, 6, 1957 to Rob R. Purdy (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Sept. 23, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Nov. 3, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Nov. 19, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Jan. 28, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Dec. 8, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Jan. 2, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Jan. 3, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Jan. 13, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Jan. 23, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., n.d (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., n.d. to John Marshall (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Rubin, Louis D., Jr., Monday (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Spiller, Robert E, March 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Starr, Elizabeth, n.d (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Stevenson, Alec B., March 28, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Stevenson, Alec B., May 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Stevenson, Alec B., May 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Stevenson, Alec B., Dee. 23, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Stewart, John L., Jan. 21, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Stewart, John L., May 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Stewart, John L., Sept. 28, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Stowe, H. Lloyd, March 27, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Tate, Allen, Oct. 27, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Tate, Allen, Jan. 27, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Tate, Allen, Feb. 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Tate, Allen, Feb. 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Tate, Allen, April 11, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Tate, Allen, April 18, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Tate, Allen, April 28, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Tate, Allen, May 10, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Tate, Allen, Oct. 25, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Tate, Allen, Jan. 14, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Tate, Allen, Jan. 15, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Tate, Allen, July 30, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Tate, Allen, Aug. 11, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Tate, Allen, Aug. 29, 1959 to Henry C. Alexander and Benjamin Tate, 2 copies (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Tate, Allen, Oct. 2, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Taylor, George Rogers, March 19, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Taylor, Walter F, May 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Thompson, E. B, Dec. 6, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Thorp, Willard, Oct. 28, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Thorp, Willard, Feb. 23, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Thorp, Willard, April 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Thorp, Willard, June 5, 1956 to Harvie Branscomb (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Thorp, Willard, Nov. 18, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Vanderbilt, Harold S, April 26, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Wade, John Donald, April 10, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Ward, John W, April 28, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Warren, Robert P., Nov. 19, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Warren, Robert P., Jan. 27, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Warren, Robert P., March 28, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Warren, Robert P., Nov. 8, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Warren, Robert P., Jan. 4, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Warren, Robert P., Jan. 14, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Waterfield, C. A., n.d (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Weaver, Mrs. Herbert, May 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Whicher, George, Oct. 25, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Wills, Jesse, Nov. 19, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Wills, Jesse, Sept. 28, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Wriston, Marguerite, Sept. 25, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Wills, Jesse, May 24, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Dave, May 1, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Dave and Candace, April 30, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Ed, April 27, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ellene, June 6, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - George, Dec. 4, 1967, to Mrs. Stewart. Possibly George Core (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Fugitive Reunion Arrangements - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Calendars of Events and Guest List, Fugitive Reunion (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Fugitive Finances. Vouchers, financial statements regarding the handling of finances for the Fugitive Reunion (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Fugitive Conference Dinner Programs enclosed in Harvie Branscomb letter, May 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Fugitive Conference Clippings, 1956 Jan 20 to June; Undated (Box 2, Folder 53-55)
- Fugitive Reunion Photos Taken by Merrill Moore (Box 2, Folder 56-57)
- Book Reviews - Pertaining to R. C. Beatty’s column (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Stewart’s Class Roll Books, For years 1947, 1955, 1956, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Articles about Stewart (2) (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Pamphlets (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Photograph of Donald Davidson effigy (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Miscellaneous - mainly mailing lists (Box 2, Folder 63)